Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - SIXTEENTH (QUEENS) REGIMENT LIGHT DRAGOONS (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - 3. 1792, Feb. 10.Norwich. [16th Lt. Dragoons] to Lt. Lee. Thetford. D.S. of C. Stone. Boyce sends Beating order and insgructions.
    - 4. 1793, Feb. 18.Barnet. [16th Lt. Dragoons] to Lt. Lee. N.P. Orders. D.S. of C. Stone. King's order and instructions for raising three additional troops for 16th.
    - 5. 1793, Apr. 18.N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons] Orders unsigned. Embarkation instructions. Lt. Lee on Betty, dress, etc. to leave from Blackwall.
    - 6. 1793,N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons] to Lt. Lee. N.P. Recruiting Instructions. D.S. of C. Stone and forms of returns.
    - 7. 1794, Apr. 1.[St. Amand]. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Orders of number of horses, Officers can draw rations for.
    - 8. 1794, Dec. 3.[Hettesen?]. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Copy of letter to Mr. Hunter. [Hetteson?]. real cause of Hunter leaving 7th foot.
    - 9. 1795, Mar. 10.16th Lt. Dragoons. D.S. of Wm. Lee. Lists of debts and credits from Feb. 23.
    - 10. 1795, May 19.[Bümmerfstede?]. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Document in French. statement re: two guns lost or missing from house of Johann Endwin Neumann, etc.
    - 11. 1795, Nov. 15.Continent. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Return of horses lost.
    - 12. 1795, Nov. 24.Scharmebeck. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. List of debts and credits of Detachment.
    - 13. 1795, Dec. 6.[Twielerfett]. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Regimental charges, account in German or Dutch, signature illegible.
    - 14. 1795, Dec. 7.Stade. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. A.D.S. of George Martens, account of cost defrayed at Hollern.
    - 15. 1795,N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Distribution of regimental charges.
    - 16. 1796, Mar. 22.[St. Albans]. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Return of horses lost.
    - 17. 1796, Apr. 11.N.P. 16th Lt. Dragoons to Secretary at War, true copy of anonymous letter s. Wm. Lee. haven't received money as ordered by Cathcart, no liberty.
    - 18.
    - 19. 1796, Apr. 20.Newbury. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Proceedings of Regimental Court Martial against Francis Dunn, true copy by Wm. Lee, the anonymous letter.
    - 20. 1796, Apr. 24.N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Account of sums due from and to various persons.
    - 21. 1796, Apr. 24.N.P. 16th Lt. Dragoons. List of debts and credits of four troops arrived from Continent. D.S. of C. Stone.
    - 22. 1796, Apr. 30.Newbury. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Copy of R.O. Dunn and Rowse and anonymous letter.
    - 23. 1796, Apr. 30.Newbury. 16th Lt. Dragoons. State of the Regiment. D.S. of C. Stone.
    - 24. 1796,Junel. Newbury. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Monthly Return. D.S. of C. Stone. Lee on leave.
    - 25. 1796, Dec. 1.Reading. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Monthly Return. D.S. of Charles Tudor. Lee at Henley.
    - 26. 1798, Mar.Godalming. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Form of resignation.
    - 27. 1798, Dec. 7.Hounslow Barracks. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Description of remounts. D.S. of C. Stone.
    - 28. 1799, Apr. 2.Hampton Court. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Report of Committee of Officers on income tax. D.S. of C. Stone.
    - 29. 1799, June 24.N.P. 16th Lt. Dragoons. State of debts and credits.
    - 30. N.D.N.P. 16th Lt. Dragoons. Return of Draft Horses lost on Continent.
    - 31. N.D.N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Instructions for embarkation and management of cavalry on board transports, loading horses. A.N. of [Wm. Lee]. should any horses prove unruly they must be blinded... (eyes covered).
    - 32. N.D.N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Lee's account. A.D. of Wm. Lee.
    - 33. N.D.N.P. [16th Lt. Dragoons]. Lee's account. A.D. of Wm. Lee.
  - STONE (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 1. 1786, Sept. 3.Norwich. C. Stone to Cornet Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Regiment needs more recruits, instructions.
    - 2. 1787, Oct. 1.Melton Mowbray. C. Stone to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. Maj.Gardner orders Lee to join Regiment at Nottingham.
    - 3. 1789, Dec. 13.Chichester. C. Stone to Cornet Lee. N.P. A.L.S. parcel of linen, Lee's dogs live at Coffee room, fox hunting, Anson.
    - 4. 1789, Dec. 15.Chichester. C. Stone to Cornet Lee. N.P. A.L.S. sends new saddle, etc.
    - 5. 1790, July 12.Canterbury. C. Stone to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. sending puppy, Munro.
    - 6. 1790, Sept. 9.Canterbury. C. Stone to Cornet Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Lee's note refused by Donnally, Sir Robert asked for leave of absence for officers, gun lost.
    - 7. 1790, Nov. 18.Canterbury. C. Stone to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Leason and Betterson, a recruit, recruiting, Archer.
    - 8. 1791, July 19.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. horses, Lee to march to Woodton.
    - 9. 1791, Sept. 18.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. recruits, Sharpe at Yarmouth beginning his military career under Wilson, pony, Col. Gardner, Capt. Lee's horse came in second for the plate at Canterbury races.
    - 10. 1791, Oct. 12.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. orders McPherson to Norwich, Gen. to buy horses for officers.
    - 11. 1791, Oct. 14.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. Paine's wages, a charger, racing, Masons - ceremony of being burnt.
    - 12. 1791, Oct. 26.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford A.L.S. Boyce commands in Gardner's absence, horses, book on masonry, part of Masonic oath, boxing.
    - 13. 1791, Nov. 2.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. deserters.
    - 14. 1791, Nov. 5.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt.Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. Ford, horses, to see Gen. Harcourt.
    - 15. 1791, Nov. 22.Norwich. C. Stone to [Lt.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Gen. Harcourt, Lee to get new charger, enquiries after Rice, deserter, Richmond.
    - 16. 1792, Jan. 20.Norwich. C. Stoen to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. Pryor to be Cornet, Nunney, deserters.
    - 17. 1792, Feb. 10.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Lee getting better, properties of Mercury, feeding cattle, plows.
    - 18. 1792, Feb. 11.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. a charge for clothing.
    - 19. 1792, Feb. 20.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. plow for farm equipment for use at Hartwell. Harcourt.
    - 20. 1792, Feb. 29.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt.Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. farm equipment, recruits, Irish business.
    - 21. 1792, Mar. 8.Norwich. C. Stone. to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. Lee on sick leave, Drill Rolls, Barnet.
    - 22. 1792, Mar. 24.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. returns.
    - 23. 1792, May 8.Norwich. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. Inn bills.
    - 24. 1793, Jan. 24.Barnet. C. Stone to Capt. Lee. London. A.L.S. Sir Robert wants Lee to move his recruiting parties to Liecester and Coventry, promotions of enlisted men.
    - 25. 1793, Feb. 11.Barnet. C. Stone. to Lt. Lee. Stonebridge. A.L.S. leggings, order for additional troops and promotions on payment, to raise men to fight Demourier and his raggad Banditta.
    - 26. 1793, Feb. 26.Windsor. C. Stone. to Lt. Lee. Coventry. A.L.S. Mason, Archer will not sell his troop.
    - 27. 1793, Mar. 3.Windsor. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Coventry A.L.S. recruit, Ld. Herberg, Lee's recruiting duty, bounty, pardon for deserters, Smith, Sharpe, Pryor.
    - 28. 1793, Mar. 19.Windsor. C. Stone to Lt. Lee. Birmingham. A.L.S. recruiting, Sir John Wrottesley, Gen. and Mrs. Harcourt.
    - 29. 1794, Jan. 27.[Oudenarde]. C. Stone to Capt. Lee at Outposts of Belleghem [Belgium?]. A.L.S. personal, Dundas is a strange fish, death of McBride, additional officers, promotions and purchases, Jacobin papers, Smollett.
    - 30. 1794, Feb. 22.Oudenarde. C. Stone to Capt. Lee. [Tournai?]. A.L.S. packing, cantonment at [Sweveghem], copy of orders.
    - 31. 1794, July 10.Wearloo's. C. Stone. to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. retreat to Berg-Up-Zoon, joining Ld. Moira's Army, sarcastic humor.
    - 32. 1796, Mar. 3.Southampton. C. Stone to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. musician band, the C. Harcourt under orders to Embark for the West Indies, quarrel between Regiments, Choiseul and Salm Regiments dismissed, trouble with Emigrant Corps.
    - 33. 1796, Apr. 7.Henley. C. Stone to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. returns, stones lame horse.
    - 34. 1796, May 19.Newbury. C. Stone to [Maj.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Brownrigg, Dunn, court martial, politics, stable dress.
    - 35. 1796, June 5.Newbury. C. Stone to [Maj.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. racing calendar, Duke of York's decision on Dunn and Rouse, a review, uniform, Carmichael.
    - 36. 1796, June 12.Newbury. C. Stone to [Maj.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Dunn, Rouse and McKewan, transfers, Lewis interference, Lee plans to leave Regiment, Le Marchant, advice, to join Cathcart.
    - 37. 1796, Oct. 22.Weymouth. C. Stone to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. Carlo, promise of a visit from the Republicans (invasion), defenses of Island of Portland, Portugal affair given up.
    - 38. [1796?]N.P. C. Stone to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. frag. Le Marchant's book on sword exercise a plagerism, Stone's own work with sword exercise.
    - 39. 1797, Jan. 12.Weymouth. C. Stone to [Maj.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. personal, reading Voltaire and Rousseau, Harcourt not helping Lee, Portugal scheme over, Ireland, Directory, news of old friends, Le Marchant's book, Carlo.
    - 40. 1797, Feb. 27.Weymouth. C. Stone to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Affleck. invasion rumors, the Pope's affairs.
    - 41. 1797, Apr. 16.Dorchester. C. Stone to [Maj.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Paget and Le Marchant gone from 16th, Lee's predicted promotion, his own prospects.
    - 42. 1797, Aug. 20.Dorchester. C. Stoen to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. jackets, Duke of York to visit camp, Prince of Wales already there for Field Days, a court martial.
    - 43. 1798, Dec. 14.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Regiment business, Gudgeon's case, kettles.
    - 44. 1798, Dec. 15.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. health, Gudgeon, Gen. Gwyn, Rooke.
    - 45. 1798, Dec. 25.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Queen's Bounty money, Kensington Bounty money, Rooke.
    - 46. 1798, Dec.London. C. Stone. Report of a patrol and map and an A.N.S. of Stone, patrol from Cornhill through Borough out Blackheath and return, over London Bridge, route, description, note re: plan in case of attack, etc.
    - 47. 1799, Jan. 25.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Old Windsor. A.L.S. funeral of a recruit.
    - 48. 1799, Feb. 5.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Old Windsor. A.L.S. death of Quarter Master Coulson from a fall, plight of survivors, pickpocket.
    - 49. 1799, Feb. 28.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Old Windsor. A.L.S.
    - 50. 1799, May 28.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. High Wycombe. A.L.S. practice for Review at Ashford Common, Quarter Master Lee to be dismissed.
    - 51. 1799, May 30.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. horses, books (financial etc.), Quarter Master Lee, General's lectures.
    - 52. 1799, June 13.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Stains. A.L.S. Affleck, Gen. Harcourt hurt that Lee did not come to field (day), orderly book.
    - 53. 1799, June 23.H.Q. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Hampton Court. A.L.S. meet on Ascot plain before King comes, instructions for Review.
    - 54. 1799, Dec. 1.H.Q. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. returns, Regiment business.
    - 55. 1799, Dec. 2.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. leaves
    - 56. 1799, Dec. 5.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor.A.L.S. returns of officers, Le Marchant.
    - 57. 1799, Dec. 7.N.P. C. Stone to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. discharges, states.
    - 58. 1799, Dec. 8.N.P. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. General's troop, thefts.
    - 59. 1800, Feb. 8.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. defense of Stone, deserters.
    - 60. 1800, Feb. 9.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. misunder-standing.
    - 61. 1800, Feb. 18.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. London. A.L.S. prisoner Smith, press gang, Mr. Orme.
    - 62. 1800, Feb. 20.Hounslow Barracks. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. London. A.L.S. regret most sincerely that you [Lee] have left... Regiment, friendship, etc.
    - 63. N.D.N.P. C. Stone to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Capt. Boyce, Col. Gardner, Foster, turkies, pocket book.
    - 64. N.D.Reading. C. Stone to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Sweepson, etc., injured horse, coldness between Lee and Affleck.
    - 65. N.D.N.P. [C. Stone] to Lt. Lee. Coventry. cover and P.S. Sir Robert recruiting.
    - 66. N.D.N.P. C. Stone to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. prisoner Smith, Mr. Orme, copy of letter to Affleck, workmen.
  - T (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - 1. 1798, June 21.[Grosvenor Place?]. James Tadloo for Mr. Tattersall to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. a draft refused.
    - 2. 1800, Nov. 29. Rockingham. John Taggart to [Wm. Lee]. [Rockingham]. A.L.S. altercation with O'Reilly, does not recognize Lee's authority.
    - 3. 1800, Dec. 1. Rockingham. John Taggart to Wm. Lee. [Rockingham]. A.L.S.
    - 4. 1794, Feb. 5.War Office. R. Taylor to Samuel Hawker. Audenarde. A.L.S. accounts, recruit Worthington.
    - 5 & 6. 1787, Apr. 14.Geneva. Abm. Terroux l'ainé to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French and cover, Mr. Perlet comedian, making a watch, has made watches for Duke and Duchess of Gloucester and Duke of Bedford.
    - 7. 1787, May 15.Geneva. Abm. Terroux (elder) to M. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. in French. descriptions of watches, will make one for Lee.
    - 8. 1787, May 30.Geneva. Abm. Terroux (elder) to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French, making watch.
    - 9. 1787, Dec. 11.Geneva. Abm. Terroux (elder) to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French, watch.
    - 10. 1788, Apr. 1.Geneva. Abm. Terroux (elder) to M. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. in French, Lee likes watch, method of payment.
    - 11. N.D.N.P. [Abm.] Terroux [l'ainé] to M. Lee. Strasbourg. Cover.
    - 12. 1797, Oct. 29.Wallingford. George Thomas Thomas to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. a prisoner.
    - 13. 1799, Feb. 26.[Cursila] St. [Mor.] Thomas to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. writings.
    - 14. 1794, Oct. 14.Elten. Thomas Tiademan to Officer Commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. Arnham. A.L.S. quarters.
    - 15. 1799, May & June.N.P. M_____ Tinson to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.D.S. account with attached clipping
      re: submitting accounts to Estate trustees.
    - 16. N.D.N.P. Tichfield to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. [Name of Sir John Dashwood appears at bottom of note]. A.N.S. notice of and invigation to annual meeting of the Buckinghamshire Independent Club.
    - 17. 1797, June 10.Henley. Lewis Tombs to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. Duffin, marriage.
    - 18. 1797, June 12.Henley. Lewis Tombs to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. marriage settlement.
    - 19. 1791, June 3.Park Place. Frs. Tomkins to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. medical advice - absolute abstinance from women, medication.
    - 20. 1791, June 4.Park Place. Frs. Tomkins to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. strong symptoms of a Pox, medication, diet.
    - 21. 1791, June 9.N.P. Frs. Tomkins to Capt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. medication.
    - 22. 1791, Oct. 22.Park Place. Frs. Tomkins to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. medication.
    - 23. N.D., Jan. 29.London. Wm. Tomkinson to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. re: a surteon's certificate.
    - 24. 1789, Nov. 30.N.P. Thomas Tuck to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. financial business.
    - 25. 1790, July 20.N.P. Thomas Tuck to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. financial business.
    - 26. 1792, Feb. 2.Cleveland Row S.t. James. Thomas Tuck to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. financial business, Lee ill.
    - 27. 1792, July 16.London. Thomas Tuck to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. financial business.
    - 28. N.D. N.P. Thomas Tuck to Wm. Lee. Kings Arms [Bageshot?]. A.N.S. visit Mr. Fiott.
    - 29. 1797, May 23.Reading. Charles Tudor to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. re: return of bayonets.
    - 30. 1796, May 26.Marlbro. Richard Turpin. A.D.S. certificate of settlement of accounts, prisoners Dunn and Rouse.
    - 31. 1796,N.D. N.P. Richard Turpin to Maj. Lee. Newbery. A.L.S. re: Gen. Harcourt's orders, horses.
    - 32. N.D. N.P. P. Tytler. to Dear Chevalier. A.D.S. plan for an augmentation of the Army, show to Gen. Abercrombyl
  - THOMPSON (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - 1. 1790, Feb. 4.London. Thomas Thompson to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. cannot get Lee a Lieutenantcy,promotions.
    - 2. 1793, Jan. 2.[London] Thomas Thompson to Lt. Lee. Barnet A.L.S. Capt. Bradshaw.
    - 3. 1793, Nov. 23.London. Thomas Thompson to [Wm. Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. cannot get Lee a Majority, promotions.
    - 4. 1796, July 9.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Carnarvon. A.L.S. Lt. Collcy waiting for Lord Cathcart's answer, exchanges.
    - 5. 1796, July 25.London. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Carnarvon. A.L.S. Col. Dickson, exchange.
    - 6. 1796, Aug. 3.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Carnarvon. A.L.S. Col. Dickson, Lord C. has no objection.
    - 7. 1796, Aug. 18.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Weymouth. A.L.S. Col. Dickson, Lt. Col'cy in Ld. Cathcart's Regiment.
    - 8. 1796, Sept. 23.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Weymouth. A.L.S. Col. Dickson.
    - 9. 1796, Sept. 28.London. Thomas Thompson to Maj. Lee. Reading [actually at Dorchester]. A.L.S. Col. Dickson in most unpleasant situation.
    - 10. 1798, Dec. 8.N.P. Thomas Thompson to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. col. Long, an exchange.
    - 11. 1798, Dec. 10.N.P. Thomas Thompson to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S.
    - 12. 1799, Jan. 7.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. business re: exchange with Col. Long.
    - 13. 1799, Feb. 2.London. Thomas Thompson to Col. Lee. Windsor A.L.S. Long delines.
    - 14. 1799, Feb. 16.N.P. Thomas Thompson to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. re: exchange.
    - 15. 1799, Apr. 9.[London]. Thomas Thompson to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Capt. Murray, Lt. Col. Hughes, Sir Charles Marsh.
    - 16. 1799, Sept. 3.[London]. Thomas Thompson, Jr. to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. Col. Colton, exchange.
  - U, V, W (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - 1. N.D. Park Place. G. [V.V.] Jr. to sir Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. neighbor.
    - 2. 1788, May 19.Brandebourg. Vette to M. Lee. Paris. A.L.S. in French, two horses.
    - 3. 1798, Jan. 4.N. [Audley] St. J.C. Villiers to Lt. Col. Leigh. N.P. A.L.S. re: a commission for Sgt. Dickens, Harcourt and 16th are models for his regiment.
    - 4. 1791, June 6.London. [T.] Wake to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. has paid a draft and a bill.
    - 5. 1798, Sept. 12.Panton St. Wakelin and Garrard to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. sent gold snuff box, silver clasp and belt, furniture.
    - 6. 1790, May 14.Panton St. Wakelin and Tayler to Capt. Lee. Epsom. A.L.S. gold box - estimates.
    - 7. 1799, May 14.Bloomsbury. Mr. Watt to Col. Lee. Hanover Sq. A.L. financial.
    - 8. 1793, Feb. 8.London. J. Weatherby to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. accounts, horses, Gipsy.
    - 9. 1799, [Nov. 4?].Windsor. Anne Weaver to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. asks help in recovering a debt owed her by Mr. Thornton.
    - 10. 1798, Apr. 2.London. [Anna J.?]. White to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. account.
    - 11. 1792, Mar. 22.N.P. J. White to Capt. Lee. Thetford. A.N.S.
    - 12. 1797, Dec. 7.London. Jos. White to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. bill.
    - 13. 1798, Apr. 30.N.P. Jos. White to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. wants account settled.
    - 14. 1798, June 29.N.P. Jos. White to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. received payment.
    - 15. 1799, Sept. 7.London. Joseph White to Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. velveteen breeches.
    - 16. 1798, June 5.London. Mathew Wilks to Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. account.
    - 17. 1799, June 12.Henley. J. Williams to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. Lees-Harper affair - assault.
    - 18. 1790, Mar. 26.Lewes. Richard Williams to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. bill.
    - 19. 1795, Dec. 20.Kinston. Richard Williams. copy of Capt. Popham's General Orders Nov. 24, 1795 re: masters of transports.
    - 20. 1790, Dec. 23.Chatham Barracks. George Williamson to Collyer Esq. London. A.L.S. dending accounts for raising Independent Co. for Cornet Lee.
    - 21. 1796, Mar. 8.Soho Sq. Daniel H. Wilson to Capt. Lee. St. Albans. L.S. send account of Camp equipage, bills.
    - 22. 1799, June 13.Soho Sq. Daniel H. Wilson to Lt. Col. Lee. Hounslow Barracks. L.S. bill for camp equipage for 1794, for Messr. John Trotter and Co.
    - 23. 1790, Feb. 26.London. J. Wilson to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. charger, cost, feed.
    - 24. 1792, Nov. 24.N.P. J. Wilson to Lt. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. meet to talk over proposal, Smollett at the White Bear.
    - 25. 1794, May 12.Ayr North Britton. Jas. Wilson to Capt. Lee. London. A.L.S. Lee offering to raise a Regiment, recommends Brent as agent, Lord Chomley.
    - 26. 1800, Mar. 20.N.P. John Wilson to Wm. Lee. A.D.S. wire bill, note 12/17/00: this bill appears to be exorbitant.
    - 27. 1798, Nov. 26.South Molton St. M._____ Wilson to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor.A.L.S. furniture, (saddle trappings), saddle.
    - 28. 1798, Oct. 17.Chancery Lane. Row'd. Wimburn to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. want money.
    - 29. 1795, Mar. 30.War Office W. Windham to Lt. Gen. Harcourt or Officer commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. Continent. A.L.S. marked copy, raising four regiments of Dragoons.
    - 30. 1796, Sept. 30.War Office. W. Windham. Circular, copy, scarcity of wheat over, increase bread ration, allowance stopped.
    - 31. 1789, Nov. 30.[Minories]. Thomas Windsor to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. wants payment, Jake's note.
    - 32. N.D.N.P. Thomas Windsor to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S.
      re: payment of note.
    - 33. 1789, Nov. 9.London. R. Wogden to Wm. Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. repair of rifle.
    - 34. N.D.N.P. _____ Wood to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. and copy of Lee's reply in Lee' s hand, June 29, money, a wager on marriage.
    - 35. 1787, Aug. 28.Paris. John S. Wood to Wm. Lee. Strasbourg. A.L.S. parcel. Sir Edm. Affleck, James, Capt. Vassar.
    - 36. N.D., Mar. 4.Bath. John S. Wood to [Wm.] Lee. N.P. A.L.S. refusal of Clark, Bagshot Club.
    - 37. 1798, Dec. 17.Symonds Inn Coffeehouse. [Mr. Woolsey] to George Lee. Stone. A.L.S. business.
    - 38. 1788, [Oct. 3?].Magdebourg. Wrede to Lt. Lee. Brunswick. A.L.S. in French. financial.
    - 39. N.D. Aug. 23.Magdebourg. Wrede to Lt. Lee. Brunswick.A.L.S. in French. needs money.
    - 40. 1799, May 9.N.P. George Wright to Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Woolsey, financial business.
    - 41. N.D.[Richard _____] George Wright to Wm. Lee. Strand Coffee House. A.L.S. financial business.
    - 42. 1799, Apr. 29.Horse Guards. W. Wynyard to Lt. Col. Lee. L.S. Lee to be pupil of Gen. [Janisse?] approved by [Duke of York].
    - 43. 1778, Dec. 2.Waltham House. Amelia Yonge to Master Lee.. N.P. A.L.S. sends painting of dog, George better, mentions dogs at Hartwell.
    - 44. 1790, Oct. 14.War Office. George Yonge to Cornet Lee. N.P. L.S. King approves Lee's raising an Independent Co. of Foot, conditons: number of officers and men, pay, expense allowance, height and age, time limit.
    - 45. 1790, Oct. 22.War Office. George Yonge. Ptd. Instructions to Officers raising Independent Companies of Foot, Chatham Barracks, Capt. Williamson 70th Foot paymaster, Col. Fox Cmdt. of Barracks, necessaries and clothing.
    - 46. 1793, Feb. 26.War Office. George Yonge to Lt. Lee. True copy, s. C. Stone, pardon for deserters.
  - WADE (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 1. 1798, Dec. 29.London. Emelia [Wade] to [Wm. Lee?]. London. A.L.S. in French, has not called, asks reason.
    - 2. 1799, Jan. 9.King St. Emelia Wade to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Comte de Roggendorff, Hamburg mails.
    - 3. [1799], Jan. 13.London. Emelia W[ade] to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Count Roggendorff, personal.
    - 4. [1799], Jan. 26.N.P. Emelia Wade to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. apology, Roggendorff, Kent, Lee's financial troubles.
    - 5. [1799], Apr. 7.N.P. Emelia Wade to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. Eliza who has seen that inprincipaled fellow Roggendorff, financial transaction, Kent, King, Baronne Kourkheim.